let questions13 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "blood",
        answer: "A. Blut",
        options: [
            "A. Blut",
            "B. Wunde",
            "C. Verletzung",
            "D. Infektion"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to burn",
        answer: "B. brennen",
        options: [
            "A. löschen",
            "B. brennen",
            "C. ersticken",
            "D. fritieren"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "cell",
        answer: "D. Zelle",
        options: [
            "A. Kiste",
            "B. Schachtel",
            "C. Raum",
            "D. Zelle"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "to contain",
        answer: "B. enthalten",
        options: [
            "A. ausschließen",
            "B. enthalten",
            "C. verbergen",
            "D. vermeiden"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "correct",
        answer: "A. korrekt",
        options: [
            "A. korrekt",
            "B. falsch",
            "C. ungenau",
            "D. zweifelhaft"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "crop",
        answer: "C. Ernte",
        options: [
            "A. Produkt",
            "B. Samen",
            "C. Ernte",
            "D. Dünger"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to demand",
        answer: "B. fordern",
        options: [
            "A. anbieten",
            "B. fordern",
            "C. bitten",
            "D. vorschlagen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "equal",
        answer: "D. gleich",
        options: [
            "A. unterschiedlich",
            "B. ungerecht",
            "C. selten",
            "D. gleich"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "to feed",
        answer: "B. füttern",
        options: [
            "A. hungern",
            "B. füttern",
            "C. dursten",
            "D. kaufen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "hole",
        answer: "A. Loch",
        options: [
            "A. Loch",
            "B. Hügel",
            "C. Welle",
            "D. Hohlraum"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "to increase",
        answer: "B. erhöhen",
        options: [
            "A. verringern",
            "B. erhöhen",
            "C. stabilisieren",
            "D. beibehalten"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "lord",
        answer: "C. Herr",
        options: [
            "A. Bauer",
            "B. Ritter",
            "C. Herr",
            "D. König"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "to owe",
        answer: "D. schulden",
        options: [
            "A. schenken",
            "B. leihen",
            "C. sparen",
            "D. schulden"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "position",
        answer: "C. Position",
        options: [
            "A. Bewegung",
            "B. Platz",
            "C. Position",
            "D. Richtung"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to raise",
        answer: "A. heben",
        options: [
            "A. heben",
            "B. senken",
            "C. drücken",
            "D. ziehen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "responsible",
        answer: "B. verantwortlich",
        options: [
            "A. sorglos",
            "B. verantwortlich",
            "C. unzuverlässig",
            "D. unsicher"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "sight",
        answer: "D. Anblick",
        options: [
            "A. Gefühl",
            "B. Ton",
            "C. Geruch",
            "D. Anblick"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "spot",
        answer: "B. Stelle",
        options: [
            "A. Fleck",
            "B. Stelle",
            "C. Linie",
            "D. Punkt"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "structure",
        answer: "C. Struktur",
        options: [
            "A. Material",
            "B. Fundamente",
            "C. Struktur",
            "D. Oberflächen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "whole",
        answer: "B. ganz",
        options: [
            "A. halb",
            "B. ganz",
            "C. Stück",
            "D. Teil"
        ]
    }
];
